{
    "subject": "resource/Nahim_Abraham",
    "predicate": "ontology/relation",
    "object": "resource/Salem_Abraham",
    "human_readable": "Nahim Abraham is related to Salem Abraham.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9670831561088562,
            "question": "Is there a familial connection between Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9588941931724548,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9508242607116699,
            "question": "What kind of relationship does the statement 'Nahim Abraham is related to Salem Abraham' imply?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9451772570610046,
            "question": "Are Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham known to each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.944094181060791,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the association between Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9380138516426086,
            "question": "Do Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham share any common relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9344727993011475,
            "question": "Who is Nahim Abraham related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9266325235366821,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about the connection between Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9007090926170349,
            "question": "Is there a family tree that connects Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8088999390602112,
            "question": "How close are Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham based on their relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nahim Abraham is related to Salem Abraham.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4978_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a family tree that connects Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4978_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more details about the connection between Nahim Abraham and Salem Abraham?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4978_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Nahim Abraham related to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4978_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4978_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents mention Nahim Abraham as the great-grandfather of Oofie Abraham (also known as Malouf Abraham Sr.).\n* The documents also mention Salem Abraham's grandfather being Oofie Abraham.\n\nBased on this information, it appears that Nahim Abraham is related to Salem Abraham through his grandson Oofie Abraham, making them distant relatives.\n\nTherefore, the answer in JSON format is:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the family lineage and relationships, indicating that Nahim Abraham is the great-grandfather of Salem Abraham. Therefore, the statement that Nahim Abraham is related to Salem Abraham is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}